Hurt them before they hurt you.
Everyone Is Going to Die is a horror, thriller,
drama film directed by Craig Tuohy.
On his daughter's birthday, a wealthy father's reconciliation
attempt is hijacked by two female burglars.
A shakedown evolves into a lethal cat-and-mouse as hidden motives
emerge, culminating in a life-altering revelation.
Comedy, played by Jaime Winstone.
Daniel, played by Brad Moore.
Tragedy, played by Chiara D'Anna.
Imogen, played by Gledisa Arthur.
Young Tragedy, played by Lila Lasso.
Phil, played by Richard Cotton.
The Monkey is a 2025 American comedy horror film
written and directed by Osgood Perkins.
Based on Stephen King's 1980 short story, the film stars Theo James in a dual role as twin brothers whose lives
are turned upside down by a cursed toy monkey that causes random horrific deaths around them.
Tatiana Maslany, Christian Convery, Colin O'Brien, Rohan Campbell,
Sarah Levy, Adam Scott, and Elijah Wood also star.
The Monkey was theatrically released in the United
States by Neon on February 21, 2025.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and has grossed
$68.9 million worldwide against a budget of $10–11 million.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.